{"data":[{"question":"She _____ a cup of tea for me.","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"3","explain":"\n - 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"This thing is ______ of gold.","a":"done","b":"have","c":"made","d":"making","answer":"3","explain":"\n- We use \"make of\" when refer to kind of material used to creat something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Are you going to ______ this translation?","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use the verb 'do' when someone performs an action, activity or task.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I'll _____ the shopping tomorrow.","a":"do","b":"have","c":"make","d":"doing","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use the verb do when someone performs an action, activity or task.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't _____ a hole in the wall!","a":"make","b":"have","c":"do","d":"made","answer":"1","explain":"\n- 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She ______ the beds East night. ","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Idiom \" make (up) the bed\" to smooth and arrange the covers on a bed so it is ready for someone to sleep","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm going to _____ the shopping.","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We use the verb do when someone performs an action, activity or task","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"She has been _____ the shopping all morning.","a":"do","b":"doing","c":"made","d":"making","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the verb 'do' when someone performs an action, activity or task","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Don't ______ war, ______ peace!","a":"do\/make","b":"make\/do","c":"do\/do","d":"make\/make","answer":"4","explain":"\n- 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I ______ some tea last night.","a":"do","b":"make","c":"made","d":"did","answer":"3","explain":"\n- 'Make' is used when refer to constructing, building or creating","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"10","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}